#### Contact

3036417202 (Mobile) mikebannoura@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mike-b-170475197 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Marketing Training

Leadership

# Mike Bannoura

--

Aurora

## Summary

Self-motivated, in-house designer and printer for Bethlehem Handicrafts who has worked with many different applications, such as Adobe Photoshop and Indesign. Basic knowledge of SEO skills with many different platforms, such as Google, Amazon, and Shopify. Quick learner who is willing to enhance skills in coding and SEO.

## Experience

BETHLEHEM HANDICRAFTS INC.

Marketing Manager/ Tour & Event Coordinator
September 2003 - Present (17 years 3 months)

Aurora, Colorado, United States

More Than A Perfume General Manger September 2009 - May 2018 (8 years 9 months) Lakewood, Colorado, United States

Managed four stores at More Than A Perfume

- Trained new staff to be highly efficient on POS system
- Accurately took weekly inventory
- · Marketed stores across different platforms, both online and physical
- Designed all posters and physical advertisements using programs such as Adobe Photoshop and Indesign
- Through my desire to learn more and my quick learning skills, I learned a vast amount of knowledge about perfume in a short amount of time
- · Drew in new customers with my advanced knowledge of perfume

### Education

Beit Sahour Orthothox High school High School Diploma, high school (1999 - 2003)